module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'The Ayatollah Khomeini was the religious leader of which country during the 1980s?', 
    a: 'Iran',
    b: 'Argentina',
    c: 'Iraq',
    d: 'India',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these is a real language?', 
    a: 'Europeaans',
    b: 'Hollandiaans',
    c: 'Antarctikaans',
    d: 'Afrikaans',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which country is also known as Burma?', 
    a: 'Angora',
    b: 'Myanmar',
    c: 'Taiwan',
    d: 'Thailand',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which planet is the largest in size?', 
    a: 'Uranus',
    b: 'Neptune',
    c: 'Saturn',
    d: 'Mars',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which country did the Magna Carta originate in?', 
    a: 'France',
    b: 'England',
    c: 'Italy',
    d: 'Spain',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the highest number on the pH scale?', 
    a: '7',
    b: '14',
    c: '10',
    d: '12',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was in 1893 the first country to allow women to vote?', 
    a: 'Canada',
    b: 'United States',
    c: 'Australia',
    d: 'New Zealand',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who wrote the novel "The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn"?', 
    a: 'Harper Lee',
    b: 'Mark Twain',
    c: 'William Faulkner',
    d: 'Ernest Hemingway',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'A file with a ".rar" extension is most similar to which other type of file?', 
    a: 'zip',
    b: 'jpg',
    c: 'sys',
    d: 'txt',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Phil Collins song "You\'ll Be in My Heart" was featured in which Disney movie?', 
    a: 'Aladdin',
    b: 'Pocahontas',
    c: 'The Little Mermaid',
    d: 'Tarzan',
    answer: 'd'
  },
];